# **Brandee Cheung**

Brandeedcheung@gmail.com | 520-401-6182 Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/brandeecheung/

Website: https://brandeecheung.github.io/PortfolioPage/

# **Qualifications Summary**

Proactive and creative Software Engineer, Web Developer, Graphic Designer, and Social Media Manager adept at identifying customer needs through extensive analysis and research to consistently deliver top-notch content designed to promote brands and increase profits. Experienced in collaborating with diverse teams on projects, operations, and branding initiatives.

### **Experience**

Owner and Operator | BXDXC LLC. Media | December 2019 - Present

- Managed social media platforms (FB/IG/Google) for paid ads and promotions.
- Organized photo and video shoots, edited content using Adobe CC.
- Developed and designed effective websites, including e-commerce.

Director of Graphic Design | Social Media Manager | DYPER, GYFT, STYR Labs | Phoenix, AZ | 2018 - 2019

- Orchestrated photo shoots and created social media content.
- Increased sales through promotions and creative collateral.

• Managed large-scale ad budgets on social media platforms.

Graphic Designer | Data Analyst | Uber, Phoenix, AZ | 2017 - 2018

- Designed visuals and graphics; collected and analyzed national data.
- Created presentations and optimized Google spreadsheets.

Social Media/Design Consultant | Dreylon Vang Sequence1 Media, Mesa, AZ | 2016 - 2017

- Planned, designed, and implemented website and social media content.
- Contributed to shoot settings and edited using Adobe Photoshop and After Effects.

Manager | Events Marketing | Maya Day and Nightclub, Scottsdale, AZ | 2014 - 2017

- Worked as a bartender and server, providing exceptional customer service in a high-energy nightclub environment.
- Managed servers and coordinated events, ensuring efficient operations and a seamless guest experience.
- Coordinated staffing and events; trained staff to improve customer service.
- Managed social media platforms and created event-related content.

Graphic Designer & Social Media Intern | Soul Carrier | 2013 - 2015

- Modeled for professional photoshoots and created branded content, enhancing Soul Carrier Handbag Company's product visibility and engagement on social media.
- Collaborated with the creative team to develop and post compelling visual content, significantly increasing social media following and interaction.

#### **Education**

**Bootcamp in Full Stack Development** 

The University of Texas at Austin - Austin, TX April 2024 to Present

Bachelor of Science in Graphic Information Technology & Web Development

Graduated Cum Laude, 2017 Arizona State University - Ira A. Fulton School of Engineering, Tempe, AZ

# **Professional Training**

Advanced Social Media Strategy Training – Influential Summit Attendee, 2018

## **Technical Proficiencies**

Full Stack Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, SQL, NoSQL, Python | Adobe Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Lightroom | Other Tools: Microsoft Office, Google Suite

**Key Skills** Lifecycle Project Management | Graphic Design | Social Media Management | Brand Development | Ads & Promos | Content Production

Web Design & Development | Photography & Editing | Staff Training & Leadership | Customer Service | Data Analysis | Market Trend Research